<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>travelling on </title>
    <link>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/tags/travelling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in travelling on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 21:22:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/tags/travelling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bosnian tale</title>
      <link>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/a-bosnian-tale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 21:22:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/a-bosnian-tale/</guid>
      <description>As I may have mentioned, I am a huge fan of the Erasmus programme. It is just that I have so many amazing experiences that it drives me to search for more. Recently, I have been on a training in Banja Luka, Bosnia. It was my first time in Bosnia and I can easily say I would never forget it. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it is Bosnian magic or just the rahat lokum, but that&amp;rsquo;s the reality!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why having international friends is so cool</title>
      <link>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/why-having-international-friends-is-so-cool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 21:05:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/why-having-international-friends-is-so-cool/</guid>
      <description>Nationality- the status of belonging to a particular nation. For me this was never important. As a person who is always trying to be open-minded and respectful, meeting people with different backgrounds has always been a pleasure.
Here are some of the pros of having international friendships that I have experienced:
 1. We teach each other. It is so cool that you can teach people about your countries and they can teach you about their own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 useful travel hacks</title>
      <link>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/5-useful-travel-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 01:58:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/5-useful-travel-hacks/</guid>
      <description>Stay in hostels. This one is pretty obvious but it cannot be overstated just how much more wallet-friendly budget accommodation options like hostels are compared with hotels, resorts and rental homes. Not only are you getting lower prices (some hostel beds are literally just a couple of dollars per night), but you’re getting the authentic backpacker atmosphere, and memories to last a lifetime.
 Souvenirs are overrated. Seriously! Instead of bringing back a suitcase full of touristy paraphernalia, why not focus on collecting memories and experiences instead of material things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First things first</title>
      <link>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/first-things-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 22:15:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/first-things-first/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! Let me tell you something about myself :)
I am a very curious person and in my opinion, everyone should be. That is how we discover, absorb and grow. I think that learning should be purposeful, enlightening and thought-provoking, which is why I recommend a combination of reading and travel.
On this blog you can read about some of my experiences, but also advices about how to create your own without struggles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>