<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Motherland on </title>
    <link>https://storytellingwithElena.com/categories/motherland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Motherland on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 21:58:16 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://storytellingwithElena.com/categories/motherland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ohrid - the real Macedonian pearl</title>
      <link>https://storytellingwithElena.com/ohrid-the-real-macedonian-pearl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 21:58:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://storytellingwithElena.com/ohrid-the-real-macedonian-pearl/</guid>
      <description>I am not sure how many times have I visited it, but I know that every time is a good idea. Amazing city with amazing views that leave me amazed every time like it is the first. You may get annoyed by the many tourists around you, but still be able to connect with the magic of the city.
Here are my personal 5 favorite things in Ohrid: 
 Monastery of St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pehchevo and Dracevo exploring Kavadarci</title>
      <link>https://storytellingwithElena.com/pehchevo-and-dracevo-exploring-kavadarci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 21:52:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://storytellingwithElena.com/pehchevo-and-dracevo-exploring-kavadarci/</guid>
      <description>Oh, how nice it is to have friends from all parts of Macedonia! I think that my friends Sandra and Edvin would totally agree with me. The two of them are my colleagues, who I met this year at Uni. It is weird how you immediately connect with some people.
Anyway, a week ago they came to visit me and my other friend Filip, in our hometown Kavadarci. To be honest, I really liked Kavadarci more when walking around with &amp;ldquo;tourists&amp;rdquo; and pretending to be their guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magical Matka Canyon</title>
      <link>https://storytellingwithElena.com/magical-matka-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 11:02:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://storytellingwithElena.com/magical-matka-canyon/</guid>
      <description>Matka Visiting Matka Canyon should be on top on any traveler’s bucket list to the Balkans. It is a truly sensational place. Despite mesmerizing nature, this canyon also offers an extensive list of entertaining activities travelers can try for an unforgettable adventure. Nature lovers (as myself) can climb rocks, rent a kayak or have an exceptional dining experience.
 List of activities you can do in Matka:
 Hiking on the edge of a cliff The kayak adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>