<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friends on </title>
    <link>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/categories/friends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friends on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 21:58:16 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/categories/friends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ohrid - the real Macedonian pearl</title>
      <link>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/ohrid-the-real-macedonian-pearl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 21:58:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/ohrid-the-real-macedonian-pearl/</guid>
      <description>I am not sure how many times have I visited it, but I know that every time is a good idea. Amazing city with amazing views that leave me amazed every time like it is the first. You may get annoyed by the many tourists around you, but still be able to connect with the magic of the city.
Here are my personal 5 favorite things in Ohrid: 
 Monastery of St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bosnian tale</title>
      <link>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/a-bosnian-tale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 21:22:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/a-bosnian-tale/</guid>
      <description>As I may have mentioned, I am a huge fan of the Erasmus programme. It is just that I have so many amazing experiences that it drives me to search for more. Recently, I have been on a training in Banja Luka, Bosnia. It was my first time in Bosnia and I can easily say I would never forget it. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it is Bosnian magic or just the rahat lokum, but that&amp;rsquo;s the reality!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why having international friends is so cool</title>
      <link>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/why-having-international-friends-is-so-cool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 21:05:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/why-having-international-friends-is-so-cool/</guid>
      <description>Nationality- the status of belonging to a particular nation. For me this was never important. As a person who is always trying to be open-minded and respectful, meeting people with different backgrounds has always been a pleasure.
Here are some of the pros of having international friendships that I have experienced:
 1. We teach each other. It is so cool that you can teach people about your countries and they can teach you about their own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pehchevo and Dracevo exploring Kavadarci</title>
      <link>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/pehchevo-and-dracevo-exploring-kavadarci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 21:52:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elenar3.github.io/my-blog/pehchevo-and-dracevo-exploring-kavadarci/</guid>
      <description>Oh, how nice it is to have friends from all parts of Macedonia! I think that my friends Sandra and Edvin would totally agree with me. The two of them are my colleagues, who I met this year at Uni. It is weird how you immediately connect with some people.
Anyway, a week ago they came to visit me and my other friend Filip, in our hometown Kavadarci. To be honest, I really liked Kavadarci more when walking around with &amp;ldquo;tourists&amp;rdquo; and pretending to be their guide.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>