<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>trip on </title>
    <link>https://storytellingwithElena.com/tags/trip/</link>
    <description>Recent content in trip on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 02:05:04 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://storytellingwithElena.com/tags/trip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking the streets of Belgrade</title>
      <link>https://storytellingwithElena.com/walking-the-streets-of-belgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 02:05:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://storytellingwithElena.com/walking-the-streets-of-belgrade/</guid>
      <description>A week ago, I was on an Erasmus+ training course in Banja Luka, Bosnia. Luckily, on my way back home I had the chance to visit Belgrade too. I really like when this happens- two birds with one stone. So, Belgrade is a city that my grandfather has always told me about. I think he was the one that made me so excited about it. Was it worth it? Comme ci, comme ça.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life hacks on how to kill boredom while waiting for a bus/flight </title>
      <link>https://storytellingwithElena.com/life-hacks-on-how-to-kill-boredom-while-waiting-for-a-bus/flight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 10:24:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://storytellingwithElena.com/life-hacks-on-how-to-kill-boredom-while-waiting-for-a-bus/flight/</guid>
      <description>Since I travel a lot, it is logical for me to spend some time on waiting for buses, flights, horses and other manners of transportation.
Once, while spending 12 hours on the Turkish airport in Istanbul, I came up with a list of things you can do when you&amp;rsquo;re in a situation like this.
So here it is:
 Playing tic tac toe when travelling with someone else Read a book Play games on the phone Observe other people- this proved as a really fun activity to do (at least for me) Make drawings to embrace your creativity Get something to eat Meet some new people- the airport is a weirdly good place to do this Think of opening a start-up Ask someone from a different country to teach you words in their language  Well, that is pretty much it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pehchevo and Dracevo exploring Kavadarci</title>
      <link>https://storytellingwithElena.com/pehchevo-and-dracevo-exploring-kavadarci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 21:52:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://storytellingwithElena.com/pehchevo-and-dracevo-exploring-kavadarci/</guid>
      <description>Oh, how nice it is to have friends from all parts of Macedonia! I think that my friends Sandra and Edvin would totally agree with me. The two of them are my colleagues, who I met this year at Uni. It is weird how you immediately connect with some people.
Anyway, a week ago they came to visit me and my other friend Filip, in our hometown Kavadarci. To be honest, I really liked Kavadarci more when walking around with &amp;ldquo;tourists&amp;rdquo; and pretending to be their guide.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>